♪ Then I'll look
from the door ♪
♪ Of my heavenly home ♪
♪ And pity the miner ♪
♪ That mines my poor bones. ♪
(Raj:)Okay. How 'bout
a little Miley Cyrus next?
(Sheldon:)Who's he?
(stammers)
Talk about wasted money.
(Howard:)What about the late fees
on our credit card
(Howard:)because somebody didn't pay
the bill on time?
(Bernadette:)Well, maybe I would have paid it
(Bernadette:)if I wasn't also doing
everything else around here.
(Howard:)Oh, you're saying I don't do
anything around here.
(Howard:)Look at my chore chart.
(Leonard:)She made him a chore chart.
I see it.
"Do the dishes."
There's a star right there.
(Bernadette:)That was a pity star. Putting
water in the roasting pan
(Bernadette:)and leaving it in the sink
is not doing the dishes.
(Howard:)That pan had to soak
and you know it.
(Bernadette:)Well, don't come crying to me